A good friend to meet, MBC
hello
Today too, we
Thank you for using the train
our train
The value of labor is not respected
Starting from a miserable reality
final destination
This is the train to the moon
Just
Get you to your destination safely
I won't listen to your promise that you will serve me
can't
Various hardships and adversities along the way
A bit sick
Because the same thing is going to happen.
Nevertheless, it has not been achieved yet
For those who have dreams and hopes
With imitation, quickly
Please board
train
Let's leave
can do
full-time
can be
Baby you arrived safely
Don't be nervous and fight
I will stick with you, I love you
Um, Dahye Jeong
Come in yes
You have experience as an intern at our company.
Yes, it was a process that did not exist before.
Received a good opportunity thanks to the consideration of the company.
over the past year
Here at Maron Confectionery
I worked as an intern
When you join the company
There is a product I want to plan.
Maron Confectionery
great for consumers
Although I am loved
Piri’s Market Point
The reasons are relatively lacking
So I'm an original pie
I would like to present my product
Then this
why
Kongkong Chips
About marketing points
Could you please explain the soybean chips?
The marketing point is childhood
I think it's a memory from the past
Um, an advertisement for the first color TV.
The concept is in the thirties and forties
won the hearts of consumers
I think you did a good job of eliciting empathy.
I think
Do you have any last words to say?
Do it
yes
I definitely wrote the article
I would like to join the company officially
full-time job for me
If you give me a chance to work
Ah ah
Already
It's already here. It's okay. It's okay.
Yong Da-hee
I came to my senses
What is it?
Why is my face there?
Just calm down and wait a moment
Is this a dream or something?
are you dead
Are you the afterlife or something?
You just passed out for a moment
I'm in the future, it's you
What
future me
I don't see it that way
I'm sorry, but the diet failed.
Ah, what was so delicious?
But why is it like that again?
What, is there going to be war in the future?
I'm on my way to evacuation now.
well
Okay, so where are you taking refuge?
It's not a life where there's no time to go
What happened
I'll get to the point first.
You shouldn't join this company
I came here to say that
Oh, what is that all of a sudden?
Hey, I have a full-time job here.
I know how hard you worked to become
Me too today
If you do well in the interview, you will become a full-time employee here.
It will work
Without even knowing anything
Mr. Full-time employees are also regular employees.
you
uh
You're just a bastard
In the future you will
I will continue to live like a small octopus
Nothing will happen
You will be poor all year round
No matter how hard I try, it ends up looking like this
I'll be consistently miserable
And yet you
Mr. Ha wants to join this company
Oh yeah
I have to go in. I have to go in.
What if I don’t go to work at this age?
I want to become an idol
If this is what you mean, it's Danju Hana.
Words won't work
Then just
die
Oh, why are you like this all of a sudden?
I can't see the good in people
Just stand by your mouth
Cling to the next life and die
No way
Even if I die, I have to support myself
Unemployed people never have a shortage.
I don't want to die
Dahee Jeong
It's okay
My child, Dahee, fainted.
that
I had that dream
Oh, how can I do this?
I need to go to the hospital for this.
I got stung by a bee
Now Noontaengi has become Bamtaengi
This is it
no, I'm fine
I will continue the interview.
It's a child, but still
I'm really fine
My desire to become that full-time employee is
This kind of punishment
I won't lose, please believe me
I am confident that I will do well
Did they say that desperation creates miracles?
updated every year
Amid record-high testing rates
I
I achieved the miracle of succeeding in finding a job.
Please just leave it to me.
sincerity
I will become a working Maron worker.
and
Miracles are shit
Why can't I contact you?
I’m worried about something. Please reply.
Uh uh team leader
us
It's almost time for the meeting.
It's okay, it's ahead.
No, there are only ten minutes left.
Here
This restaurant is said to be more delicious than Gangnam Bonjeon.
Without me
As a worker, this is something delicious.
I have to eat it in a snap.
Well, then you can do market research
It makes me drool.
Mistress
forward
I'll go to just ten more.
sorry
Oh wait a minute
No, don't push me
uh uh
No, let's go, my cell phone, cell phone, ah
child
Wait a minute oh no
Don't step on the child. Don't step on the child.
No no no no no
Ah
Ah, let’s sell this guy, it’s good, it’s good.
Be classy
It's late, run
IC
IC Team Leader, Team Leader, I
Ah
Come quickly, let’s go quickly
Oh, why are you drinking coffee?
Coffee is important to me
I can't get this coffee
I can't speak properly after drinking.
Wow, you will take responsibility.
why am i responsible
Wow ICIC
Ah
It's okay
yes it's okay
Is your laptop okay?
All the data is included here.
Be really okay.
be okay
Just try your best, it's okay
Let’s go, Seonhee.
Let's be patient
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
Oh sorry sorry sorry
I have to drop the child off.
Mr. Tongwoo got off. Come to the stairs.
Yes, up to the fourteenth floor.
There are only five minutes left
I'll be ready
Come quickly
bed
Ah
I have to endure it, what should I do?
The child evaluation is just around the corner.
You can't kill team leader Go.
Ah
Oh man
Kill it
ten fifty-nine minutes fifty-five seconds
fifty-six seconds
fifty-seven seconds
fifty-eight seconds
fifty nine seconds
Yes, as you can see, our company’s new product
If I am glucose
It's been a long time since I started planning and developing
price of this raw material
Because of coordination issues
The release is being delayed
On the other hand, in the case of competitor Pixa
early
Steady with grapes
I made salad and already added mango.
cherry
It's been a long time since I passed on the taste.
So I research
With the development team
Gathered the marketing team and had a meeting.
result shine
Using Muscat
We decided to develop a product
Wait yes
Shine Muscat
Oh that
Isn’t it a Japanese product?
This is Japanese
What is Japanese?
I didn't know, no, that
What did you not know?
Defender of material origin
Measures that take emotions into account are measures
Are there any countermeasures?
I think it would be nice to have
I think it would be nice to have something
No, that means
Is there anything you think would be nice to have?
Yes, that's the solution
What should I do?
attention
Here, King Gukbong’s bowl is dying.
I
You always emphasized patriotic marketing.
Team leader Cheon
yes it is
To actively utilize domestic agricultural products
Shine Musket produced domestically
You also analyzed the current situation.
yes
Even in Korea
Shine already from 2006
Muskets are being produced
Jinto Buri
Ours is good
Republic of Korea
uh
I guess it's not that bad
Report to us when samples come out.
Thank you for your hard work
Vice President, I will work hard.
thank you
Thank you, government, madam.
Thank you. I will work hard.
thank you
Ha ah are you okay?
Ugh
Ah ah ow
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm drinking again
If you suck, I'll shut up.
Haha, it’s really Eunsang this time too
If it weren't for Mr.
It's a big day
It was obvious
I lived today again because of Unsang.
thank you
Hey
Let’s go to the president and eat again.
How much did you eat yesterday, Father?
How was the foreign meeting? Hallback.
It's real, it's real
See, I'll have plenty of time.
Yes, your team leader is the best.
You are a great man
Thank you Dahye
Mr. Yes
But you still have a conscience
I know you're thankful
No
I'm fine
Hey kid, look at this.
uh
kill
I bought it when I went to Japan over the weekend.
Japanese craftsmen are making only the present
They say it's the best product
Everyone
I think it would be good if you taste it hehehe
Wow
I feel like this because of Dahye
Because it flies
Oh, I’m glad the meeting went well today.
Arigato thanks to Dahye’s support haha
That kind of bastard
Mr. Ddonggu
Ddonggu, try one of these too.
That guy's shit
Mr. Dahye
yes no
Now don't be shy, hiya hiya hi
Ah yes um
Oh wait a minute yes
Dahye
Mr. Yes No
Not Dahee, but Dahye Hae and Dahye Dahye
Oh yes
Oh I really
two people
I'm confused about the name, so it's a big problem.
Really Dahye
From now on, Mr.
I'll call you Mr. Shit.
Yes, why am I round?
no
Wherever I look, it looks round
Boy, what does that look like?
really just
I go by feeling.
So what is that
And I like Dahee more
It's because I'm used to it
six months longer than that round letter
I joined the company first.
Because I need it for work
Oh Dahee
Yes, shit writing
shit writing
Yes yes yes
Oh, that's good. If you call me like this, it's all sorted out.
Mr. Tongwoo
No, I'm fine.
Still try one
You worked hard today, yeah
uh
Um yes then me too haha uh
Don't eat, don't eat
Wait a minute
hold on to it for a moment
I have to share it with my superiors.
Making life at our company easier
I guess not
So I'm on the 18th floor
Oh, why are you like that?
no
How about giving Bin Soo-hee coffee?
Wow, this is a shitty condition
Look at this
This is from our team.
Rain, get out of the way, just give it to me for a moment.
uh team leader
Are you okay?
Oh, okay then, I’ll give you this.
uh uh
Mr. Dahye
One quarter from the accounting team
He said he would like to see my work performance report.
Oh, that'll come later.
uh meeting now
He said he wanted to see it before.
Oh well, just about anyone.
Mr. Dahye
Oh really
annoyingly
I really ordered all the results
Room at the end of the hallway on the 18th floor
Where is the end room?
Excuse me
Yeah
Is there anyone?
Huh
Wow
what is here
Wow, it’s a complete palace.
Huh
Wow Mr.
uh
Awesome
I saw this in an ad
Wow this
my three feet
It was a salary.
No, this is precious
Why is your body here?
Ah, a new employee lounge was created.
Okay then, where can I go once?
Ugh.
oh
tea
Wow
Ah good
Oh my oh my
Wow
Wow Mr.
Oh my, it’s so cool.
Wow
Ah
Oh, I understand why it’s expensive.
Hey
Oh, you just held my bones tight.
Why are you like this?
What is it
Why is this stopping?
What is it, lady?
Yeah
Yes, my remodeling went well.
Ha, would you do this?
I didn't need it
What is it
Ah, but
That nameplate is burdensome, so that’s it.
I changed it a bit
This wasn't the break room, yeah
What should I do, what should I do, what should I do?
First, let’s wake up naturally.
She doesn't move
Mr. Lee
What is it
Oh, where are we going?
Mistress
um
Ta-da surprise
You were surprised, just surprised.
Okay, let's go out.
Where did you see it?
You crazy kid
Why are you sitting there again?
Ah, why can’t this be erased again?
Mr.
Hey there
Why are you doing this? Are you okay?
The evaluation sheet came out.
Bayahuro evaluation season has arrived!
The company did last year
during the year
Five about employees
graded grades
Congratulations Dahye among us
The seed is the first to give
No, ah
It doesn't make sense haha anyways Dahye
I heard you're humble haha
How is everyone today?
I'll buy you lunch
To put it simply, this is
You really come this time
It means you did a good job
Then I'll buy the coffee.
How about you do some work?
It means that I admit it.
Oh, I'm a little bit today
I'm busy so I don't think I can go with you.
Enjoy your meal
This took a lot of effort
But no way
I'm not satisfied here
It means
and
no further explanation
omit
please
OK
ha
Ah
Ah Mr.
Ah huh
Lunch is yum yum
Disassuring yum yum yum
I ate a lot
Oh Bob
If you eat a lot, your teeth will become strong.
My biceps are soggy.
Slippery huh
Awesome
lower earth
I guess the warming is happening because of you
So hot, so hot
This Weekend
Oh, we didn't forget our promise.
Oh, I'm going to do a couple item with you.
A board is also my
My sunglasses too
Song again bye haha
What else is there to buy?
I just want to say goodbye to my love
Haha
Mr. Song
I finished organizing this month's expense statement.
uh
It's almost done.
three days ago
I thought you said it was almost done.
Oh, that's it
Uh huh
It was almost done three days ago.
Uh, it's almost done now.
This is
There is a difference like this.
The net cost is here haha
Uh oh anyway
Whatever it is
Whatever it is, it's not done yet.
Uh, I'm just kidding right now.
no no
After work
Please finish everything beforehand.
Okay
yes
Johnny Eunsang's rating
It's not a door this time either
I'm not like that
It was decided above.
Ah, then the company
I'm not saying I'm quitting.
Our team is
They don't even provide supplements.
Silver award for daily wages
Let's say you quit even the seeds.
I guess I turned around because I couldn’t move.
I put myself first, I’m fine
Me too, let’s go get something to eat.
I have something to say to you
When to eat
Even if you eat it, peel it first before eating it.
What did you get, sister?
Why are you asking the obvious?
My sister is okay too.
Same thing for three years
It's been like this for three years, really Eva.
It's called Ssamba.
three years
Has it already happened like that?
It seems like
Come with me from the shackles of greetings
Two people who do it
Kang Eun-sang and Kim Ji-song
I met these two
It's already been three years
What is this child singer?
Haha, let's go by bus.
Haha sorry for this
Ah, the bus suddenly spread out.
I'm sorry, yeah yeah yeah
Wow sorry
Hey, anyone going to Gangnam, get here
I live in Gangnam Gangnam
Gang Gang I want to live in Gangnam
I live in Yeoksam-dong.
Oh oh ta ta ta
Apgujeong since I was five years old
I lived
Oh yeah yeah
Manager, apartment move-in date this week.
You know there's a meeting.
There is no Sillim-dong
From Sillim-dong to Sillim-dong
Sillim-dong I live near Sillim-dong.
There is a Chinatown
In front of Korea University, in front of Korea University
Manager, I even went to the Kyungin University club.
went
we go too
Team leader Go, team leader
Even if it’s Team Leader Go
Real team leader, team leader
Our Fourteenth Princess
I love you I love you
Let's go
Fourteen Period
among us
No one lived in the Gangnam area
I didn't even go to a prestigious university.
More than anything, we
The three were not from public recruitment.
So to speak, we
Out of their own league
Congratulations
I'm floating around
Should I say that they were easily private bonds?
We meet like this every time
Ah, I see.
By all means
It's like studying the rest at school.
I did some studying
Ah yes
Oh, I'm okay with it too.
Haha
go in
Have a glass of soju with your rib soup
Okay let's go
What that
In common, like this
Although we became friends
Please wait a moment
wait a minute
I've had enough
Enjoy your meal
thank you
Wow wow
I want to upload it again
With a big start announced
Ice skating queen once again
to write a new history
I took on the challenge
two thousand eighteen years
Pyeongchang
Securing the right to participate in the same Olympic Games
Player Lee Sang-hwa
This makes the Olympics
I decided to challenge myself for amnesty.
rival
and Lee Sang-hwa
a real legend
No but
I thought I heard you were injured.
Isn't that too much? It's too much.
third year
Our beggar is being tolerated
The same reality is impossible
What should I do?
Non-public bonds
They say they won't give me recognition for promotion.
Ah, that's right
It's already hard to live
It's not good, so I'm dying, I'm dying.
You're telling me to die, really.
Ah, it went up
Dogs are expensive, Mrs. Lee
Boss, it's bad, it's 7,800 won.
I'll pay by card
It's 3,700 won.
Please take a coupon
It's 4,500 won. Lots of whipping.
Hey
Are you the kids who say soup is expensive?
It's more expensive than a meal
so easily
This is the water of life
I need to drink this much
I'll last until I get off work.
Um oh yeah
I don't drink it every day
Once or twice a week
Well this is okay
uh
What is this? I didn't see this.
You noticed
It's new this season. It's pretty.
It's pretty. Hey, where do you get the money?
Always remove new items
in shoes
What kind of money are you using in your wallet?
Lend me a loan from our bank
What
Citizens Bank also provided great help.
Haha how are you doing haha
It turned around
Former Team Leader Song, those dirty hands
Like this
Just because I didn't pull it out
I'm proud of it, yeah
Sweet like this
I need to eat and go shopping, right?
Otherwise
Team Leader Song, in response to that, I just resigned.
That's right, today isn't pay day.
You can't resign.
It's payday
This
Knock knock
Yeah
child
IC
It's been a while since we've been in touch
Is that bastard a classmate?
please tell me to come
It's not pretty
None of my bank account information is good.
Ah, why do we have to meet like this?
I decided to go to Pyeongchang and snowboard.
you are in beijing
Baby and I haven't broken up yet
Break up
Let's kiss our love for 1,000,000 years
Sister knows love
Something like love doesn't make money
I'm not sure
I know some other things
What else?
It's a coin
Yeah I know, I know
I'm talking about coin karaoke.
I'm not Kono, I'm not Kono
Ah, the laundromat
Not the i-coin laundromat.
yes
Something like virtual currency
In other words, it's the same thing
Hey you
how do you do that
Are you thinking of comparing it to game money?
What's wrong with Dahye?
Oh I'm talking to you now
Dahyeya
What's wrong with you?
uh
Oh no no
Why are you worried?
Baby, it's not like that.
fact
Actually
Byeongjun
get married
uh
No, it's almost time to get married.
No way, I got proposed to you
No, what kind of sudden rush is this?
what is marriage
No, no, no
Oh and what can I say
Rather than that marriage
living together
If you do it first, then you will be living together.
Huh ah
What do you mean no?
Why does he stop talking to people like this?
What
I'm off work today
Hey, why is he like that?
Huh
Haha
What is all this, team leader?
Why am I Jihoon Kim?
The end is that I write my home address.
Write down the office address
sorry
I'm really, really sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry. Bring this Chorong.
slowly
Oh wait a minute
Mr. Kim Ji-seong, really.
Oh, why are you doing this?
Oh, I'm really sorry.
I need some
It's not that I want to do that.
What should I do? What should I do? Oh, should I give it to you like this?
Ah, Mr. Yoonjae.
pas
Oh no
Then just me
Let's go, see you next week
Have a nice weekend, Dahee.
Ah yes yes
Going
Come in
Bye bye
go
Sounds fun.
The power is off
Connected to voice box
Call charges will apply after the beep.
Hey there
Are you my boyfriend?
Because I went missing.
Please find me
Haha
Oh, it's okay
I only do this one thing.
Yeah yeah
Ah, mom
Oh really, why are you like this?
Ah, it’s like this again
Oh, you're cooking.
Haha, it's like this
Oh no food
Okay haha
Hurry and pour that wine
Wine, yes, that one
This will be done soon
Where is this opener?
Oh, that's right, I forgot to buy it for you.
I can't do it without you
I don't think it will work
Look, if I do that
I'll go get it right away, okay.
Come back
Yeah come quickly yeah
Yeah
At first
I thought it was some kind of event or something.
Tomorrow is my birthday
Well, if you wait a little bit
Grab something like flowers and a cake and voila.
surprise
I thought you would come in, but
He's not coming
It doesn't come even after an hour
It doesn't come even after two hours.
I got a feeling, this is something
It's wrong
That opener
Living tall
Didn't see a single man.
From then on
I was looking for Byeongjun.
When Byeongjun smokes
I also went to the playground I used to go to.
Just in case
So I went to Byeongjun’s house.
Byeongjun
Byeongjun Lee
Oh, Mr. Lee is really noisy.
Oh, let's get some sleep.
sorry
But
It wasn't there, anywhere
After that, I even had an absurd thought.
I'm listening
What an absurd idea.
Because he wouldn't have stood in the sky
Didn't it fall to the ground?
Yes it's a sinkhole
Why does it look like that movie?
I just broke my leg
The building collapsed and I was trapped.
Disaster on that star
There are all sorts of situations.
About a sinkhole
It's quite a possibility
Isn't it?
But even if I keep waiting
No announcement from the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport
There wasn't one
Ah, what were you waiting for again?
Then later
I would like to contact the Ministry of Defense.
Why in the Ministry of Defense?
I guess that
I think it was their doing.
It's an alien
UFO comes down and takes Byeongjun.
They took me away
It's very unlikely
Isn’t it true?
Oh well
we that
Just a little more
Talk about potential
Let's try it
At the time of disappearance
My boyfriend
Was there anything different from usual?
The man said he was having a hard time or was angry.
There was a situation that made it possible to fly
Uh, it was just a little ordinary, yeah that day
That day
If I had to pick one, it would be
When you go out on a date that day
I keep
I asked them to turn on the hotspot.
I have a budget phone
I use up all my data.
Ah, data yes yes yes
And that team leader
No, I just cursed at the boss.
Well, that's a bit annoying
I think it might have happened
And eat
I paid for the coffee
I paid 1,000 won with coins.
I don't have enough check cards.
and
again
Oh again, yes
that
That's it
ha
uh uh
Ah
This
It's time to go home and go to school
Should I move at this point?
I have to think about getting married soon.
Ah
Oh, what a shitty corner of the house
There is something good
Raise the monthly rent
There is no threshold in the bathroom
Me too today
How can I take a shower for fear of overflowing?
I don't know if you asked for it
I'll put some waterproof tape on it soon.
i do it
no
It's going to fall again soon anyway.
just
Oh, I'm hungry. I'm not hungry.
Hey, should I eat something?
uh uh yeah
That wine is good
Let’s grill and eat that eel together.
It's cold, so I need to take care of myself.
What are the housing prices in your neighborhood?
Well, just
Ah, I see
It's easy to go to work and it's nearby
There are many hospitals
It seems like a good neighborhood to live in
Is that so?
Um that
내가 혹시
자기네 집으로 들어가면
아이 결혼하자는 소린 아니고
그냥 일단 같이
살아 보기라도 하면
뭐 생활비도 아끼고
거창할 필요는 없잖아 응
소소하고 무난하게
뭐 결혼이야 천천히 하면 되니까
어 오픈어가 없네
아 참 그 사 준다는 걸 깜빡해
없이는 못 따지 안 되지
있어 봐 나 금방 사 올게
어 그래
다녀와
그렇게 나가서는 연락이 끊긴
거예요
내가 내 상황을
객관적으로 정리해서 말하는 동안
깨달았다
병준이는 떠난 거다
나랑 결혼하고 싶지 않아서 개새끼
어머 어머
어머 죄송합니다
저도 모르게 아니에요 위로가
돼요
아유 안 아
죄송합니다 아니 아니요 저기 그
민중의 지팡이가 그런 놈팡이
잡는데 귀한 시간 쓰시면 안 되죠
I'll pretend there was no report.
Oh ah
That
Hey there
Fighting
Ah, fighting
For your information, my sister liked whipped cream.
sorry sorry
I was confused with another room.
sorry
ha
thank you
Hey, what are you going to do if Dai notices?
Post it in group chat room
A
You must have noticed, sister.
I put it
What did you buy so much?
It was money to be ripped off.
It's fun if we all use it together.
Oh, sister, it’s late, it’s late, it’s late
let's go quickly
Put it in my sister’s bag.
Oh my goodness
Ah me ah me Dahye what
once
What are you
I'm sorry Dahye, I told you
I have no shame in holding it in
yes
If you have shame, you should do it.
I came back after 24 years.
That's not right
It's only been one day
To me, one hour felt like a year.
uh
Oh, I'm sorry.
Real beauty
I'm sorry, I should have done that yesterday
come to me
Still come back to me
I want to marry you
I don't love you
I'm sorry
Should have done it all yesterday
Please don't misunderstand my feelings
i love you
But the more I love you, the more I
Ha, I will continue to regret you.
What
I thought a lot
What if we get married?
Will it be as good as it is now?
Can I be happy?
Oh but it won't work
What's wrong with us?
You too
The one born with me in my mouth is a black snake.
When you get married, it's worse than when you live alone.
I'm going to have to throw it away hard.
you can do that
why not
I also go to work
It's an unofficial recruitment.
It's hard to get promoted
At least
With your salary now, we can expand the size by half.
Pay it back by getting married and try it temporarily.
One way or another
notice
I can't go any further because I can see it.
Ha, how do you raise a child alone?
Stop it, I will die alone.
It has to be like this
Even if I told you to stop
I can't buy a house in Seoul
Even if you taste it and wash it, there is no water
A house overflowing with
I can't buy one space
Just perfect
eat and die
Earn as much as you can until retirement age
You just have to work like a dog
Ha, that's a good life for you.
I really like that
Oh really
When you talk like that
Give me some alcohol
Sober mind
It's so hard
sorry sorry sorry
I'm really sorry
uh
you
I'm crying, I'm not crying because of you
It's because of me
Because I'm so pathetic
I couldn't help but like things like you
my situation
There was only something like you
my
my life
It's so pathetic
Dahye, oh me
Get out of the way
happy birthday happy birthday
One day I saw myself like this
There is an enemy
Was it a dream?
Or so sick of it
Did he foresee this repeating reality?
whatever it is
life is real
It sucks
come out
Ah
Ugh
Ouch
Oh, why are you being so rude?
Oh no
I saw it somewhere. Um.
What is breakup?
Like this
When it was time to leave, each person
Was it going on the road?
So which one is better?
jesus buddha
Anyway, it's a deal that the mind knows.
Socrates or Plates
Anyway, who said that?
hey what does that mean
Hey
I can't do that short thing
Are you struggling like this after memorizing it?
Still, I want to tell you that.
You cry so much
Ugh
Oh, don't keep crying
What's the point of crying about this?
Then this judge
I enjoy it
Should I give you something to wake up to?
Baby, don’t cry because of that guy.
Please think about something nutritious.
Something that really helps in your life
A bit more serious, yeah
futuristic
For example
Now if it’s coins and sweets
Ah, who keeps interrupting people?
I guess
I think I should say this
It's true
Oh baby
Oh I'm done now
no what
I had a difficult time
I solved it
I'll see you there
I love you later
Mr. Geese
Chew this
pup
I caught him and put his head in the water of the Han River.
shoulder water
Hit your feet too
Should I soak it and make boiled pork and eat it?
See Mr. Lee
Oh, call me
Why are you swearing so cruelly?
Hey
An app that shares your location with that bastard
I said, get me wanted right now.
Well, he kept turning his phone off.
But why
Anyway
This is the same as the Asari.
Let's really go dancing
I know that
Here is the blue crosswalk signal
Much more than a minute
yes
But why
during that time
what can we do
Oh what
Mr. Why
The child's hair is good
Oh, it smells really good, what is that?
Why is it there?
Byungjun Lee, you are so sick
Why do I keep going out? I only see you.
i want to die
Why do you believe in something you can't even see?
No, I'm sorry about the pickled radish.
Then, even if you are fifteen, you must be an orphan.
Do you make money like this?
money
event
you are so ordinary
They say a lot of things keep happening
wide me
I only have states
It's a mess
The thing that doesn't suck is woo woo woo woo
That's not my brother's name
It's my name right
oh hi
Hey
subway
The guy who said transfers were such a bother
This kind of transfer is really fast.
Oppa, this is Hansuk’s love affair.
That's not it, no, no
Oh, the man I fall for every night
Was that a love affair?
It was convalescence
Hey Jeong Da-hee
What are you saying like that?
In that sense
what did you do yesterday
You know that health food I ate?
Oh that
I'll give it to you now, yeah
It's this
eat
Uh oh
Fighting Fighting Fighting Fighting
Fighting
Fighting Fighting
Is it spicy?
It tastes sick
What are you doing?
What now
It came in very naturally
Hey
Lying down
Just for one day
No, leave your stupid house alone.
Why do you always come to my house and make a fuss?
Where did you see it?
who
brave woman
If you're that bad, you're brave.
What bullshit
Hey, what a shame haha
Hahahaha
Hmm
Still, it's my birthday, so I have to do what I have to do.
victory
Hey
one two three
Ah
Thank you hehehehe now, sister, sister
You have to make a wish.
Just living an easy life
But life is really
Why is it so difficult?
Oh, that's right
I don't want anything
This life cannot be revived
Because it already seems like a mess haha
Let's go home now. It's cold.
Sister, this
Have some cake and go
Sister, let’s go and eat together, sister.
Hey, I need to put a cake in this.
It's there
me today
There was something I wanted to continue talking about.
Oh, it's ruined
Oh why what again
again
Why do you keep interrupting people?
No, look over there.
There's a shortcut here
Ah, I don’t know the last train.
Oh, hey, let’s go together, oh, that, oh, oh
Hey
Wait a minute, okay
oh oh
What is it, Jinho, really?
Ah
Ah uh
It's okay today, it's okay, it's okay
Oh really
Why did you suddenly run out?
Wake up kid
Ah ah ah
Ah ow
No, be careful, be careful
Let’s eat, let’s eat, quickly, quickly, quickly
Hohohohohoho ah
Ah ah ah
What should I do with my child?
Anyway, nothing is going to work.
from one to ten
It was just completely ruined.
Mr. Lee
I didn't ruin it
Ah
Oh, I’m surprised. Hey, I’m screaming.
We have it too
What happened today?
To turn this game around
a secret weapon
one room
I just tried it
One punch to a heartless world
Even though I stole three corns
This familiar misfortune
A person without money or money
Because I believed it was fate
But Eunsang is now
talking
For us too
There is one room
Blow away this painful reality
refreshing
We also have one room
I see
I am flying
Uh uh uh uh
uh
Hey guys we
I didn't know at the time
This moment is our
Let's coin
That you will change your fate
Please just leave it to me.
sincerity works
I will become Maron’s worker.
Dahye Jeong 3
years later
Mr. Jeongdal
How do you think you live?
Should I say it's your wish?
yourself
There won't be a future to hope for
What do you think it will be like in three years?
Oh, I just
star ride
Without any problem
I want to live, but it's boring
Living comfortably
How do you live?
I don't know either
If you get stung by a bee, go to the hospital right away.
life you can go
Isn’t it?
Actually, right now I
It hurts
But I'm afraid I'll fall if I keep going like this
Then, starting next month
really
For paying the medical insurance costs,
To someone
It's so obvious that it's boring
I'm just so desperate
So now I live
I'm a bit miserable
So it won't be like this after three years.
Don't become particularly miserable because of money
So that I can live such an easy life
Can you please add it to me?
As long as the company sticks
Can you live whatever you want?
Yes of course
You make money
uh
I think Dahyun is like an older sister to me.
I turn my eyes to that kind of day school
Do something like coins
Can you see people?
Even though I promised myself that
Are you buying this?
Nothing works
There isn't one
I saw Dr. Han and Dahye during the interview.
I didn't do that
But how will you remember me?
three years ago
You had an interview with me.
No, you might like it
Why can't I like it?